Bisma Mirza

Marketing Graduate

I am a quick learner, detail-oriented, and possess excellent communication and interpersonal skills. I am confident that my passion for marketing, combined with my education and experience, will make me a valuable asset to any organization. I am excited to take the next step in my career and make a positive impact in the world of marketing.

bismaashraf690@hotmail.com



Karachi, Pakistan

03351020717



in linkedin.com/in/bisma-ashraf-792195213

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Business Administration

Bahria University Karachi Campus

3.58

Intermediate

02/2019 - 01/2023

Meritorious College

07/2016 - 07/2018

Α

Matriculation

Happy Home School

01/2004 - 01/2016

Α

WORK EXPERIENCE

Social Media Account Executive Synage Global

03/2023 - 05/2023

- Develop, implement and manage social media strategy.
- Prepare monthly content calendars and insight reports of brands.
- Work with designers to ensure content is informative and appealing.
- Communicate with industry professionals and influencers via social media to create a strong network.
- Hands-on experience on digital platforms like Facebook, Instagram, LinkedIn, Twitter etc.
- Creating reels and lifestyle shoots for brands.

Social Media Marketing Intern Digital Software Labs

03/2022 - 04/2022

- Manages social media accounts and posts content on different platforms of different clients.
- Monitor social media activities to find adaptable ideas and campaigns that perform well.
- Support the marketing team in administrative tasks.
- Brainstorms campaign ideas

Verification & Recruitment Intern

Prime Human Resource Pvt Ltd

08/2021 - 09/2021

- International and Local Calling in Financial and Non-financial organizations.
- Bulk and permanent hiring for different clients.
- Scheduling and taking interviews of the candidates.

CERTIFICATIONS

Google Ads Video Certification

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Marketing Gala (02/2019 - 03/2019)

- We opened the food brand in which we offered variety of products and choices to customers.
- Also, We have to engage customers to sell products by using our marketing strategies.
- With great efforts of my team we were able to get everything done in appropriate manner. Also awarded as a best brand in that Gala

Brands Approval (08/2021 - 09/2021)

- Contacted many USA & UK brands for wholesale brand approval.
- Filled the brands contacts forms and made deficiency reports.
- Scanned pricing sheets for profitable products.

Brand Management Report On L'Oréal Paris (09/2020 - 10/2020)

- We did market research in loreal Paris foundation.
- In this report we made new marketing strategies, pricing strategies, new trends.
- Every team members gave their recommendation

Conducted 1-1 Interview At JS Investment (05/2019 -06/2019) (05/2019 - 06/2019)

- Conducted 1-1 interview of Chief Finance Officer (Zafar Iqbal)
- In interview we asked him about management styles, employee engagement, Policies that they use in their organization.

SKILLS

- -Inclusivity & Diversity Focused
- -Time Management
- -MS Office
- -Virtual Assistant

REFERENCE

• References available on request